{
  "users": [
    {
      "username": "test",
      "email": "test@test.com",
      "password": "test",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "SE",
      "email": "ax@test.com",
      "password": "test",
      "id": 2
    }
  ],
  "admin": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@admin.com",
      "password": "admin",
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "login": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "username": "test",
      "role": "users",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "username": "test",
      "role": "users",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 11
    }
  ],
  "subjects": [
    {
      "SubjectName": "Angular",
      "Questions": [
        {
          "question": "AngularJS is a ____",
          "answer_1": "JAVA Framework",
          "answer_2": "Javascript Framework",
          "answer_3": "HTML Framework",
          "answer_4": "SQL Framework",
          "correctAnswer": "Javascript Framework"
        },
        {
          "question": "AngularJS is perfect for?",
          "answer_1": "MPAs",
          "answer_2": "DPAs",
          "answer_3": "CPAs",
          "answer_4": "SPAs",
          "correctAnswer": "SPAs"
        },
        {
          "question": "Among the following, on which architectural pattern is AngularJS based?",
          "answer_1": "Decorator pattern",
          "answer_2": "Observer pattern",
          "answer_3": "MVVM architecture pattern",
          "answer_4": "MVC architecture pattern",
          "correctAnswer": "MVVM architecture pattern"
        },
        {
          "question": "Choose the correct syntax for writing AngularJS expression.",
          "answer_1": "[expression]",
          "answer_2": "{{expressions}}",
          "answer_3": "{{{expressions}}}",
          "answer_4": "{expressions}",
          "correctAnswer": "{{expressions}}"
        },
        {
          "question": "Choose the reactor which is used to bind the application data to the HTML view in AngularJS.",
          "answer_1": "ng-bind directive",
          "answer_2": "ng-model directive",
          "answer_3": "ng-init directive",
          "answer_4": "ng-app directive",
          "correctAnswer": "ng-bind directive"
        },
        {
          "question": "Choose the correct statement about the lowercase filter.",
          "answer_1": "it is a function that takes text as input",
          "answer_2": "the lowercase filter converts a text to lowercase text",
          "answer_3": "both a and b",
          "answer_4": "none of the above",
          "correctAnswer": "the lowercase filter converts a text to lowercase text"
        },
        {
          "question": "Choose the advantage of Angular JS among the following.",
          "answer_1": "it provides reusable components",
          "answer_2": "it uses dependency injection and makes use of separation of concerns",
          "answer_3": "it is unit-testable",
          "answer_4": "all of the above",
          "correctAnswer": "all of the above"
        },
        {
          "question": "The functionality of angular controllers in the application is",
          "answer_1": "an angular controller is used for displaying the data",
          "answer_2": "an angular controller is used for controlling the data",
          "answer_3": "both a and b",
          "answer_4": "None of the above",
          "correctAnswer": "an angular controller is used for controlling the data"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is not present in the dependencies section of package.json ?",
          "answer_1": "Ongtsc",
          "answer_2": "Obazel",
          "answer_3": "Ongcc",
          "answer_4": "None of these",
          "correctAnswer": "Ongtsc"
        },
        {
          "question": "If we need to opt out type-checking in TypeScript to store any value in a variable whose type is not known right away, We can use?",
          "answer_1": "void keyword",
          "answer_2": "any keyword",
          "answer_3": "null keyword",
          "answer_4": "None of these",
          "correctAnswer": "any keyword"
        },
        {
          "question": "Under the default implementation of ErrorHandler prints error messages to",
          "answer_1": "the text file",
          "answer_2": "None of these",
          "answer_3": "the console",
          "answer_4": "the log file",
          "correctAnswer": "the console"
        },
        {
          "question": "How to install TypeScript transpiler ?",
          "answer_1": "Either using Visual Studio or npm",
          "answer_2": "None of these",
          "answer_3": "using Visual Studio",
          "answer_4": "using npm",
          "correctAnswer": "Either using Visual Studio or npm"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is a valid string type in TypeScript ?",
          "answer_1": "bookName = 'Angular IJI Development';",
          "answer_2": "None of these",
          "answer_3": "B0th are valid - var bookName: string = 'Angular'; and bookName = 'Angular IJI Development';",
          "answer_4": "var bookName: string = 'Angular';",
          "correctAnswer": "None of these"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which command is used to manually compile a TypeScript source file into ES6, if using Typescript",
          "answer_1": "tsc",
          "answer_2": "Typescript",
          "answer_3": "node",
          "answer_4": "typescript",
          "correctAnswer": "tsc"
        }
      ],
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "SubjectName": "Javascript",
      "Questions": [
        {
          "question": "Javascript is an _______ language?",
          "answer_1": "Object-Oriented",
          "answer_2": "Object-Based",
          "answer_3": "Procedural",
          "answer_4": "None of above",
          "correctAnswer": "Object-Oriented"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
          "answer_1": "var",
          "answer_2": "let",
          "answer_3": "Both A and B",
          "answer_4": "None of above",
          "correctAnswer": "Both A and B"
        }
      ],
      "id": 2
    }
  ],
  "UsersSubjects": [
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "username": "test",
      "role": "users",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "username": "admin",
      "role": "admin",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "username": "test",
      "role": "users",
      "userID": 1,
      "id": 7
    }
  ]
}